ANDRE STÁBILF

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

SOCIAL

arquiduqueandre@gmail.com



andrestabile.esy.es

PROFILE

Highly qualified, researcher, autodidact and experienced in short term projects, individually and in groups. Have varied knowledge in information system, administration and human learning. In love with product creation and inspired by innovative environments. Fluent in Portuguese and English, advanced Spanish.

EXPERTISE

User Experience Design User Interface Design Adobe Creative Suite HTML CSS lavascript Team Leadership Project Management

SKILLS

Leadership Communication Research Technical Writing Strategic Planning

EXPERIENCE

2016 - Present

Elevtor | Cofounder and UX/UI Developer

- Planning investments, spending analysis and results evaluation on User Experience.
- Managing teams of designers and developers in product building.

2015 - Present

Freelancer | User Experience Designer

- Execute interactive and visual design as part of a multidisciplinary teams.
- Research and development in interactive design, visual design, UX and new technologies.

2015

Software Engineering Research Group | Project Manager

• Complete do over of an ERP developed by members of the Software Engineering Research Group, utilizing profound concepts of User Experience.

2012 - 2014

Database Research Group | Quality Manager

• Building of more than 15 large systems since the requisite determination with stakeholders to the delivery of executables, focusing in documentation, interface and tests.

EDUCATION

2016

User Experience Design School

Springboard

2012 - 2015

Bachelor of Computer Science

São Paulo State University - UNESP

VOLUNTEERING

2017

AIESEC | Vice-President of People Management

- Plan, organize and realize recruitment, induction and education plan for AIESEC members.
- Control Human Resources Data: member retention, development and productivity.